<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>The Krueger Report</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/updates.xml" rel="self" />
<link href="https://krueger.report" />
<id>http://notes.krueger.report/</id>
<updated>2017-02-27T17:00:00Z</updated>

<entry>
<title>Updates For February 27, 2017</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/introduction/updates" />
<id>https://krueger.report/updates/20170227</id>
<published>2017-02-27T17:00:00Z</published>
<updated>2017-02-27T17:00:00Z</updated>
<content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<h3>A New Format... Again</h3>

<p>Before getting into other topics, I would be remiss to not talk about the slightly new format on here. When I created this site, I initially started it out as a standard blog, where I would post every few weeks. These were my &quot;notes&quot;. After 10 months of doing this, I created the &quot;book&quot;, which took the same content, but acted as my most up-to-date versions of those writings. I tried to make the two sit together, but this ended up being more work than I enjoyed.</p>

<p>The &quot;book&quot; portion of the site ended up being the more fun part for me. While I do not wish to put unfinished work up, the nature of some of what I enjoy writing about is that it will never be complete, or it would become outdated at some point.</p>

<p>The solution I have come up with is to combine the two into one. Now, The Krueger Report is just one piece that more closely resembles the &quot;book&quot; portion of the old version.</p>

<p>My writing will still be the same as it was before. The way I write is to focus on a single topic each month, and work on completing that. I will be maintaining that schedule, but instead of a separate &quot;notes&quot; section, I will post updates to both this page as well as a new Atom feed that can be subscribed to. This feed will show periodical updates, linking to the new pages I have written, along with quick summaries of what I have updated. Much like this very update.</p>

<h3>Software Tools</h3>

<p>Anyone who knows me knows that I am incredibly picky about what software I use. I will painstakingly research as many possibilities as I can for any application type that I use.</p>

<p>There has always been a set of criteria that I follow, but I wanted to write down exactly what they were, instead of just leaving it a bit nebulous in my head. The last few months, I made notes about my thinking as I evaluated new applications. When reviewing these notes, I found that they were all related to five specific criteria.</p>

<p>In <a href="https://krueger.report/technology/software-tools">Software Tools</a>, I wrote up what these five criteria are. In the future, this will also be where I delve into specific examples of applications that I currently use, and how they make use of all of the rules set forth.</p>

<h3>Updates</h3>

<p><a href="https://krueger.report/gaming/games-i-have-played/">Games I Have Played</a> saw the biggest change this month. I began to add console systems and mobile games to the list, as well as breaking out the list into different sections based on the platform the game was played on. This page is time consuming, as I have played a lot of games in my life, but it is one of my favorite to go back and research, just to remember again the many games I have played but since forgotten. There is a lot of work to do yet on this list, but it is shaping up to being closer to where I want it to be.</p>
]]>
</content>
</entry>

</feed>
