<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>The Krueger Report</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/updates.xml" rel="self" />
<link href="https://krueger.report" />
<id>https://krueger.report/</id>
<updated>2017-05-14T08:45:00Z</updated>

<entry>
<title>Updates For May 14, 2017</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/introduction/updates" />
<id>https://krueger.report/updates/20170514</id>
<published>2017-05-14T08:45:00Z</published>
<updated>2017-05-14T08:45:00Z</updated>
<content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Iced Coffee</h3>

<p>One of the first things I do every morning is start drinking a nice cool cup of coffee. It helps start my day quicker and jump right into the tasks that I have for the day. Over the last few years, I have worked on perfecting my <a href="https://krueger.report/health/iced-coffee">Iced Coffee</a> recipe, and have found an easy and consistent way to make it exactly to my liking.</p>

<h3>Favorite Readings</h3>

<ol>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2017/05/amazon-alexa-ads-voicelabs/">15-second ads coming to Amazon’s Alexa</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2017/05/success-the-nintendo-playstation-prototype-is-fully-functional/">18 months after discovery, the “Nintendo PlayStation” is finally working</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/apple/2017/05/apple-buys-beddit-a-sleep-tracking-company-with-existing-apple-watch-app/">Apple buys Beddit, a sleep-tracking company with existing Apple Watch app</a></li>
<li><a href="http://leancrew.com/all-this/2017/05/engineering-and-yellow-lights/">Engineering and yellow lights</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.wired.com/2017/05/hundreds-apps-can-listen-beacons-cant-hear/">Hundreds of apps can listen for marketing 'beacons' you can't hear</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2017/may/06/dont-know-who-am-antidepressant-long-term-use">‘I don’t know who I am without it’: the truth about long-term antidepressant use</a></li>
<li><a href="https://stackoverflow.blog/2017/05/09/introducing-stack-overflow-trends/">Introducing Stack Overflow Trends</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.theverge.com/2017/4/24/15403644/microdosing-lsd-acid-productivity-benefits-brain-studies">LSD microdoses make people feel smarter, and scientists want to know why</a></li>
<li><a href="https://michaelfairley.com/blog/i-made-a-game-in-rust/">Making a game in Rust</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2017/05/measles-outbreak-rages-after-anti-vaccine-groups-target-vulnerable-community/">Measles outbreak rages after anti-vaccine groups target vulnerable community</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2017/5/8/15579810/tech-savvy-justice-democrats-bernie-sanders-the-young-turks">Meet the tech-savvy activists trying to take over the Democratic Party</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.theverge.com/2017/4/25/15408338/bike-peloton-review-indoor-cycle-live-streaming-cycling">My two-month ride with Peloton, the cultish, internet-connected fitness bike</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/?p=1094641">New Windows look and feel, Neon, is officially the “Microsoft Fluent Design System”</a></li>
<li><a href="http://scattered-thoughts.net/blog/2017/04/26/notes-on-the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world/">Notes on 'The Distracted Mind: Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World'</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2017/05/sleep-it-off-how-and-how-well-wearables-can-track-sleep/">Sleep it off: What you can and can’t learn from sleep tracking wearables</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.nationalgeographic.com/magazine/2017/06/dinosaur-nodosaur-fossil-discovery/">The amazing dinosaur found (accidentally) by miners in Canada</a></li>
<li><a href="https://tonic.vice.com/en_us/article/the-creepy-insane-and-undeniably-romantic-world-of-cryonics">The creepy, insane, and undeniably romantic world of cryonics</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2016/04/the-diseases-you-only-get-if-you-believe-in-them/479367/?single_page=true">The diseases you only get if you believe in them</a></li>
<li><a href="https://compileandrun.com/stuggles-with-rust.html">The grass is always greener - my struggles with Rust</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2017/05/ubuntu-17-04-review-this-is-unitys-true-swan-song/">Ubuntu 17.04 review: Don’t call it abandonware, per se</a></li>
<li><a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2017/05/u-k-hospitals-hit-in-widespread-ransomware-attack/">U.K. hospitals hit in widespread ransomware attack</a></li>
<li><a href="http://scattered-thoughts.net/blog/2016/10/28/vive-experiments/">Vive experiments</a></li>
<li><a href="http://kottke.org/17/04/what-is-digital-humanism">What is digital humanism?</a></li>
<li><a href="http://theoatmeal.com/comics/believe">You're not going to believe what I'm about to tell you</a></li>
</ol>

<h3>Books Read</h3>

<ul>
<li>Biopunk: DIY Scientists Hack the Software of Life, by Marcus Wohlsen</li>
<li>The Internet of Risky Things: Trusting the Devices That Surround Us, by Sean Smith</li>
</ul>

<h3>Games Played</h3>

<ul>
<li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Final_Fantasy_X/X-2_HD_Remaster">Final Fantasy X-2 HD Remaster</a></li>
<li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Little_Nightmares">Little Nightmares</a></li>
<li><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/System_Shock_2">System Shock 2</a></li>
</ul>
]]>
</content>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Updates For April 25, 2017</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/introduction/updates" />
<id>https://krueger.report/updates/20170425</id>
<published>2017-04-25T21:30:00Z</published>
<updated>2017-04-25T21:30:00Z</updated>
<content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Vitamin B12</h3>

<p>In continuing my goal of understanding the ways I can become more healthy, I spent this past month researching <a href="https://krueger.report/health/vitamin-b12">Vitamin B<sub>12</sub></a>. This vitamin is important for vegetarians like myself to stay on top of, as it is easy to become deficient in it. </p>

<h3>Favorite Readings</h3>

<ol>
<li><a href="http://www.theverge.com/2017/4/12/15265530/walt-mossberg-internet-plan-privacy-freedom">A plan to preserve the internet</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.pixelpoppers.com/2009/11/awesome-by-proxy-addicted-to-fake.html">Awesome by proxy: addicted to fake achievements</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.theguardian.com/technology/2017/apr/18/god-in-the-machine-my-strange-journey-into-transhumanism">God in the machine: my strange journey into transhumanism</a></li>
<li><a href="https://insights.ubuntu.com/2017/04/05/growing-ubuntu-for-cloud-and-iot-rather-than-phone-and-convergence/">Growing Ubuntu for cloud and IoT, rather than phone and convergence</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/security/2017/04/hackers-set-off-dallas-156-emergency-sirens-over-a-dozen-times/">Hackers set off Dallas’ 156 emergency sirens over a dozen times</a></li>
<li><a href="https://xkcd.com/1823/">Hottest editors</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XxutY7ss1v4">Is the European Union worth it or should we end it?</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.theverge.com/2017/4/4/15177856/mastodon-social-network-twitter-clone">Mastodon.social is an open-source Twitter competitor that’s growing like crazy</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2017/04/one-third-of-americans-are-willing-to-eat-lab-grown-meat-regularly/">One-third of Americans are willing to eat lab-grown meat regularly</a></li>
<li><a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2017/04/soylent-recall-dairy-accidentally-mixed-into-dairy-free-1-8-powder/">Soylent recalls powder after dairy accidentally slips into 1.8 powder</a></li>
<li><a href="http://nautil.us/issue/47/consciousness/the-deep-space-of-digital-reading-rp">The deep space of digital reading</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.adbusters.org/featured/the-lilly-suicides/">The Lilly Suicides</a></li>
<li><a href="http://daringfireball.net/2017/04/the_mac_pro_lives">The Mac Pro Lives</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20170330-the-uncertain-future-of-democracy">The uncertain future of democracy</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.bbc.com/news/technology-39641262">Tomorrow's Cities: Singapore's plans for a smart nation</a></li>
<li><a href="https://micaelwidell.com/who-will-remember-you-in-100-years/">Who will remember you in 100 years?</a></li>
</ol>

<h3>Updates</h3>

<p>I added a few more problems to <a href="https://krueger.report/programming/project-euler-in-swift/">Project Euler In Swift</a>. Since completing these, I have experimented briefly with Python and Rust, and have started to plan out doing a comparison of all these languages using Project Euler. But getting a more in-depth grasp of Swift is important before doing so.</p>

<p>AutoSleep 4.0 brought about a slight update to <a href="https://krueger.report/health/tracking-sleep/">Tracking Sleep</a>. Functionality remains the same, but the graphics of the app have been refreshed to provide for a nicer experience.</p>
]]>
</content>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Updates For April 6, 2017</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/introduction/updates" />
<id>https://krueger.report/updates/20170406</id>
<published>2017-04-06T08:45:00Z</published>
<updated>2017-04-06T08:45:00Z</updated>
<content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Project Euler In Swift</h3>

<p>Since I am not a full-time professional programmer, a lot of the code work that I do is just for fun. A lot of this consists of small projects and solving challenges and puzzles that other people release.</p>

<p>Project Euler is my main source of these types of puzzles. All of them are math problems of varying difficulty. As of right now, there are currently 585 problems to solve on there.</p>

<p>My language of choice when it comes to non-web programming is constantly changing. I enjoy seeing what is available and playing around with the different paradigms. Since it's release, Swift is a language I keep coming back to. It hits all of the right marks for me, ones that a lot of other popular languages like Python do not. For that reason, I have decided to work through all of the problems in <a href="https://krueger.report/programming/project-euler-in-swift">Project Euler In Swift</a>. One new problem a week is my current goal, which given that there are 585 problems, with more periodically being added, it will take me over 11 years to complete this exercise.</p>

<h3>Updates</h3>

<p><a href="https://krueger.report/introduction/about-the-author/">About The Author</a> was updated to include detailed information about all of my current computer systems. During this process, I did a basic benchmark of all of the systems using GeekBench 4. Seeing how all of my computing devices stack up on performance was interesting, particularly the part where my phone is now faster than my laptop.</p>

<p><a href="https://krueger.report/technology/software-tools">Software Tools</a> now displays the first selection of applications that I regularly use. Every application on there follows the principles I listed, when it is relevant.</p>

<p>This month, <a href="https://krueger.report/gaming/games-i-have-played/">my game of choice</a> was the original System Shock. I missed out on this game when it first came out in 1994, and unfortunately, it is a hard game to go back and play. It is an old school game, particularly with regards to complexity. The interface is cluttered and controls are obtuse, even by the standards of the time. Still, it was an enlightening experience, particularly to see an earlier work of Warren Spector.</p>

<p><a href="https://krueger.report/introduction/tools-used-to-create-this/">Tools Used To Make This</a> has been updated with more information about how this site functions automatically, as well as information about how I test the performance of the site.</p>
]]>
</content>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Updates For March 18, 2017</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/introduction/updates" />
<id>https://krueger.report/updates/20170318</id>
<published>2017-03-18T19:45:00Z</published>
<updated>2017-03-18T19:45:00Z</updated>
<content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Exercise</h3>

<p>In recent years, the amount of time I spend exercising has lessened. I would occasionally exercise, but it kept becoming more sporadic. Weight gain has been steady since I left college, and especially since we moved up here to Oregon.</p>

<p>In an attempt to help alleviate these problems, I looked back at how I exercised in college and recreated a similar routine. I have been following this <a href="https://krueger.report/health/exercise-routine">exercise routine</a> for a few months now, and while I am still perfectin certain aspects of it, I have found it easy to keep up with and it is helping my weight and overall health.</p>

<h3>Updates</h3>

<p>AutoSleep is now the app I use for <a href="https://krueger.report/health/tracking-sleep">tracking my sleep</a>. There are a number of improvements that it has over Sleep++, with the main one being that I no longer have to manually enable it every night and disable it every morning. It just works™. </p>

<p>6 months ago, I wrote my first steps to completely <a href="https://krueger.report/technology/logging-off-facebook">logging off Facebook</a>. Since then, I have missed Facebook not in the slightest. The other night, I reopened my account just so I can go in and initiate the full deletion of the account. Before doing that, I looked around at the news feed and the walls of a few of my friends. My decision to cut back on social media has been solidified. Facebook has not changed in the 6 months since I stopped using it, and it probably never will. My life is better without it.</p>

<p>I am at the end of building the list of <a href="https://krueger.report/gaming/games-i-have-played">Games I Have Played</a>. All major systems have their games entered and linked up to further information about the game. I know there are going to be random games here and there that I have not entered due to not remembering them. But as now, this is the most complete list of every game I have played. And it is much bigger than I anticipated.</p>

<p>And finally, this month's new game was <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grim_Fandango#Remastered_version">Grim Fandango Remastered</a>. Overall, it was an enjoyable game, and a fun revisit to one of my favorite adventure games of all time. But as much as I enjoyed playing through it, adventure games of this style do not hold me the way that they used to. I love everything about this game, except for the gameplay. Too bad it's not a movie, or a TV miniseries, or something else along those lines.</p>
]]>
</content>
</entry>

<entry>
<title>Updates For February 27, 2017</title>
<author>
<name>Paul Krueger</name>
</author>
<link href="https://krueger.report/introduction/updates" />
<id>https://krueger.report/updates/20170227</id>
<published>2017-02-27T17:00:00Z</published>
<updated>2017-02-27T17:00:00Z</updated>
<content type="html">
<![CDATA[
<h3>A New Format... Again</h3>

<p>Before getting into other topics, I would be remiss to not talk about the slightly new format on here. When I created this site, I initially started it out as a standard blog, where I would post every few weeks. These were my &quot;notes&quot;. After 10 months of doing this, I created the &quot;book&quot;, which took the same content, but acted as my most up-to-date versions of those writings. I tried to make the two sit together, but this ended up being more work than I enjoyed.</p>

<p>The &quot;book&quot; portion of the site ended up being the more fun part for me. While I do not wish to put unfinished work up, the nature of some of what I enjoy writing about is that it will never be complete, or it would become outdated at some point.</p>

<p>The solution I have come up with is to combine the two into one. Now, The Krueger Report is just one piece that more closely resembles the &quot;book&quot; portion of the old version.</p>

<p>My writing will still be the same as it was before. The way I write is to focus on a single topic each month, and work on completing that. I will be maintaining that schedule, but instead of a separate &quot;notes&quot; section, I will post updates to both this page as well as a new Atom feed that can be subscribed to. This feed will show periodical updates, linking to the new pages I have written, along with quick summaries of what I have updated. Much like this very update.</p>

<h3>Software Tools</h3>

<p>Anyone who knows me knows that I am incredibly picky about what software I use. I will painstakingly research as many possibilities as I can for any application type that I use.</p>

<p>There has always been a set of criteria that I follow, but I wanted to write down exactly what they were, instead of just leaving it a bit nebulous in my head. The last few months, I made notes about my thinking as I evaluated new applications. When reviewing these notes, I found that they were all related to five specific criteria.</p>

<p>In <a href="https://krueger.report/technology/software-tools">Software Tools</a>, I wrote up what these five criteria are. In the future, this will also be where I delve into specific examples of applications that I currently use, and how they make use of all of the rules set forth.</p>

<h3>Updates</h3>

<p><a href="https://krueger.report/gaming/games-i-have-played/">Games I Have Played</a> saw the biggest change this month. I began to add console systems and mobile games to the list, as well as breaking out the list into different sections based on the platform the game was played on. This page is time consuming, as I have played a lot of games in my life, but it is one of my favorite to go back and research, just to remember again the many games I have played but since forgotten. There is a lot of work to do yet on this list, but it is shaping up to being closer to where I want it to be.</p>
]]>
</content>
</entry>

</feed>
